

#### Contact

fernandadinitavares@gmail.com

mobile: +1 778 859 2142

## **Summary**

Graduated in Film Production in Brazil with work experience in production, film editing, still photography, art direction and specialized in Visual Effects for Film and Television here in Vancouver.

I'm a fast learner with a keen eye for details and I have an organized work methodology to create beautiful images. I'm easy going, a team player, and very diligent. Also, I like baking.

## **Experience**

March 2014 - Now

FX/Comp Artist at DHX/NerdCorps, Vancouver - Canada

2011 - 2013

Freelancer <u>Video Editor</u>, <u>Motion Graphics</u>, <u>Production</u> and <u>Art Director</u> at Prooh - DOOH Production, São Paulo - Brazil

2012, July - 2013, February

<u>Video Editor</u>, <u>Production Assisten</u>t, <u>Jr. Motion Graphics</u> and <u>Jr. Coloris</u>t at Canal Independente, São Paulo - Brazil

2010 - 2012

Freelancer as **Photographer**, **Editor** and **Art Director** for several film, television and marketing studios.

### **Education**

- 2013, March 2014, February Visual Effects for Film and Television VanArts Institute of Media Arts, Vancouver - Canada
- 2009, February 2012, January Film and Television Production Senac, Sao Paulo - Brazil

- 2011
   Photoshop CS5
   DRC School, Sao Paulo Brazil
- 2011
   Photography for Fashion
   <u>Full Frame School</u>, Sao Paulo Brazil

2012
 After Effects
 DRC School, Sao Paulo - Brazil

#### **Softwares**

- The Foundry Nuke
- Softimage XSI
- Autodesk Maya
- Adobe Photoshop
- Apple Final Cut
- Apple Compressor
- Apple Color
- Houdini

### **Portfolio**

• Linkedin: ca.linkedin.com/in/fernandadini

• Flickr : flickr.com/fernanda-dini

• Vimeo: vimeo.com/dinifernanda

## References

# Citizenship Status

Employment and education references available upon request

Permanent Resident